<string_table>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_1_title">
		<text>Clean Deal - Meet the Stalkers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_1_descr">
		<text>Got a voice message from Senya Snap - says there's a way to "make some serious cash." They're waiting for me at the Cordon, near the tunnel to Darkscape.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_title_0">
		<text>Clean Deal - Reach the deal point</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_descr_0">
		<text>There's gonna be a deal at night in Darkscape near the ruined railroad bridge - some "downed" guys will be trading various gear for money and artefacts - we need it more. But first we gotta reach the deal point.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_descr_1">
		<text>Damn, an ambush! Gotta deal with these mercs - no time to stare at the PDA!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_descr_2">
		<text>Mercs are done for - time to collect the loot - containers should be right under the bridge. After that, I should talk about splitting the loot with Senya Snap.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_descr_3">
		<text>No one leaves here alive - gotta waste Senya, Danila and Denis so no one finds out what happened here. All this loot belongs to me! And only me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_title_1">
		<text>Clean Deal - Neutralize the mercenaries</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_title_2">
		<text>Clean Deal - Find and collect the containers</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_title_3">
		<text>Clean Deal - Talk to Senya Snap</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_quests_2_title_4">
		<text>Clean Deal - Eliminate unnecessary witnesses</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_0">  
		<text>Alright, glad ya came - everyone's here: Danila, Senya, and Denis Toothless. So, here's the deal: we got a fat chance to score some serious loot, no bullshit, prolly 50k worth of gear for each of us, like really. In Darkscape, some downed bastards are settin' up a deal at night - trading artefacts for guns and gear, plus a fat stack of rubles on top - four containers total, just right for each of us. Senya kinda... let's say he "accidentally" intercepted one of 'em, and from his PDA, there should be eight guys. Well, seven, if ya count the stiff. Should be easy, four of us can waste those freeloaders no problem. So, ya in or out? No time to think - yes or no.</text>  
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_1">
		<text>I'm in, guys.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_2">
		<text>Fuck yeah. Alright, here's a radio so we can talk, now listen up - we'll wait till night in the tunnel, then hoof it to the ruined bridge in Darkscape. Long fuckin' walk, but luckily there's a stalker group at the sawmill - we can stop by if we need supplies. Once we hit the bridge, we waste those pricks, split the loot, and scatter. Oh, and one more thing - signal's shit in Darkscape, only works on high ground, and none of us got a "Signal Booster", so memorize the map while ya can. Anyway, if there's more to say, I'll tell ya on the way.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_3">
		<text>Got it - let's move, damn it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_4">
		<text>Guys, I'm swamped right now, can't roll with ya.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_5">
		<text>Fu-u-u-u-u-u-ck me sideways! Goddamn backstabbin' piece of... Ah, screw ya then. Get the hell outta here, we'll handle it without ya and make bank like crazy, while you go scavenge scraps like a damn dog.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_danilla_6">
		<text>Fine, I'm out. Later.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_start_0">
		<text>Alright boys, the stalker's with us - extra firepower never hurts. Senya, what's the word on the PDA guy?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_start_1">
		<text>Nothin' new, but got a message askin' where the stiff is. These guys are foreign I think, speakin' English. We gotta move our asses before these fuckers leave the Darkscape.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_start_2">
		<text>Relax, they ain't gettin' far from Darkscape - either run into the Sultan guys or straight into us. Whatever, let's haul ass to the tunnel and wait for nightfall.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_0">
		<text>Night's finally here... God I hate Darkscape, fucking shithole.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_1">
		<text>Perfect for your ugly ass. Just hope we don't run into any freaky shit...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_start_darkscape_2">
		<text>No shit... Stalker - lead the way! We'll follo... Blyat... Hui.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_hill_0">
		<text>Hey, stalker, the communication is good from here. Try pullin' up your PDA, check it. If there is a communication, check the map.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_stalker_camp_0">
		<text>There's a stalker camp at the sawmill, let's not make too much noise - they're chill, but we don't need any extra trouble right now.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_stalker_camp_1">
		<text>I'm already stocked up. But you stalker, might wanna grab some supplies if you need 'em - nothing but shitstorm ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_bridge_0">
		<text>Bridge ain't far now, time to kill the lights. Stay sharp and keep your eyes peeled.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_bridge_1">
		<text>God is with us...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_bridge_2">
		<text>Remember - no English.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_john_0">
		<text>Alpha Actual to Alpha One Four -  John, where the heck are you? You fucking late! The deal is already under way! I see your PDA is active - why you not answering!?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_john_1">
		<text>The fuck they yappin' about?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_john_2">
		<text>Deal's started, we gotta move our asses double-time, or we'll be chasing these fucks all over Darkscape.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_merc_dead_0">
		<text>That's it, we wasted 'em all. Stalker, go find the containers then get your ass back here - time to split the loot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_merc_dead_1">
		<text>Fuck me, last time we had a shootout like this was five years back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_phrase_merc_dead_2">
		<text>Yeah, not like roughing up those rookies back in Cordon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_dialog_0">
		<text>Bravo Actual, this is Alpha Actual - SITREP, over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_dialog_1">
		<text>Alpha Actual, this is Bravo Actual - crossing Zone Perimeter, entering AO, all Green, ETA 5 Mikes, how copy, over.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_dialog_2">
		<text>Roger that Bravo, Break.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_dialog_3">
		<text>Bravo, be advised - we have one MIA in Cordon area, proceed with caution, over</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_dialog_4">
		<text>Copy that, Bravo out.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_fail">
		<text>Well fuck you then, backstabber - no matter, we'll manage without you - more loot for us anyway.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_start">
		<text>Fuck me... Damn thing glitched! Testing, testing... Sound working? Whatever. Well... Stalker, hey there, it's Senya Snap, remember me? You delivered that package to me from Danila Extremist. Don't recall? Fuck it anyway. Listen up, got a chance to make some serious cash, I mean real fucking bank - you in? We'll be waiting at Cordon, near the tunele... Fuck, tunnel to Darkscape - get your ass here quick, we ain't waiting forever! And uh, bring a flashlight or NVGs if you're rolling in cash - we will work during night.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_alert_0">
		<text>Flash! Alpha, we have four unknown PDA signals approaching our position from Cordon area, the deal is compromised, prepare for contact!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_alert_1">
		<text>Roger that Alpha! All Bravo units prepare for combat! </text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_battle_0">
		<text>Light them up boys!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_battle_1">
		<text>Ambush! Let's fuck them up!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_battle_2">
		<text>Sniper on the bridge - keep your heads down!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_battle_3">
		<text>Suka! These bastards got top-tier gear and training - they're tearing us a new one!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_battle_4">
		<text>This is for John, motherfuckers!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_joke_0">
		<text>Bravo, be advised, visual on four unknown armed men, over!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_merc_joke_1">
		<text>Very funny Alpha, regroup under the bridge, all Green.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_0">
		<text>Alright, got all the containers. So how we splitting this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_1">
		<text>Well stalker, here's the thing...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_2">
		<text>The fuck you mean "the thing"?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_3">
		<text>You fucking snakes! Knew this was a setup from the start! You're dead, you cocksuckers! \n%c[d_orange][Attack]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_4">
		<text>The artifact container's mine, no discussion - I need 'em, and not for cash... Though if they don't work out, I'll pawn 'em off. The money goes to Denis, he wants top-notch gear. The rest we can split - see, I knew what's in these from the PDA all along, so here's your choice: \n\nThis one's got a sniper rifle, M24 chambered in .338 Lapua Magnum, one of the best in its class, I'd kill to have one myself. \n\nThat container's got gear - a sweet "Nomad" suit and three kevlar plates to stop bullets without breaking a sweat. \n\nSo what'll it be?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_5">
		<text>I'll take the "Nomad" and kevlar plates.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_6">
		<text>Gimme the sniper rifle, could use one.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_7">
		<text>Fuck your deal - easier to waste you and take it all! \n%c[d_orange][Attack]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_8">
		<text>Smart choice! Alright stalker, we better haul ass before more come for the gunfire... We'll go our way, you go yours. Later, and... thanks for the help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="fe_darkscape_cases_9">
		<text>See ya!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_speak_to_senya">
		<text>I should talk to Senya Snap first.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>