<string_table>
	<string id="st_fe_open_case">
		<text>open the case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_rock_name">
		<text>Rock</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_rock_desc">
		<text>Humanity has made use of rocks since the time the earliest humans lived. This early period, called the Stone Age, saw the development of many stone tools. Stone was then used as a major component in the construction of buildings and early infrastructure. Mining developed to extract rocks from the Earth and obtain the minerals within them, including metals. Modern technology has allowed the development of new human-made rocks and rock-like substances, such as concrete. Rocks are composed primarily of grains of minerals, which are crystalline solids formed from atoms chemically bonded into an orderly structure. Some rocks also contain mineraloids, which are rigid, mineral-like substances, such as volcanic glass, that lack crystalline structure. The types and abundance of minerals in a rock are determined by the manner in which it was formed.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_red] • %c[ui_gray_2] practical benefits: %c[ui_gray_1]none</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_case_with_rocks_name">
		<text>Extremely heavy case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_case_with_rocks_desc">
		<text>A blue case with a broken lock - anyone can open it. Incredibly heavy. Something is beating against each other inside. You can see "to Sultan" written on it side.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_red] • %c[ui_gray_2] lock is broken beyond repair\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] can be opened\n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_case_with_items_name">
		<text>Case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fe_case_with_items_desc">
		<text>A case like any other case - usually used to store and carry something valuable... Or very heavy. This particular case has no protection from curious stalkers. There is something inside.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] can be opened\n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_senya_podkidnoy_name">
		<text>PDA (Version 0.1) (Encrypted) (Damaged)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_senya_podkidnoy_desc">
		<text>A very old and extremely damaged PDA with the most basic functions, which has already gone out of fashion among many stalkers. The PDA is essential for daily information sharing. It comes with pre-installed GPS module to provide geolocation and time information to the user. Its main advantage is its low energy consumption. You can see "Senya Snap" written on it back.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] very low electric power consumption\n
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_senya_podkidnoy_new_name">
		<text>PDA (Kulon) (Encrypted)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_senya_podkidnoy_new_desc">
		<text>An extremely rare and unique model of the Kulon PDA, which can only be obtained on the Mainland. This model is ideal for the harsh conditions of the Zone - the PDA is made of a metal case with full electromagnetic shielding and total protection from moisture and dust, which is why its breakage is possible only in theory, and the touchscreen display is made of triplex glass, which makes it impossible to damage it, and is also covered with a special weatherproof film on which among other things, there are no traces and scratches. This model also has extremely low energy consumption, which allows it to run for up to a week on a single pair of batteries. All ports for communication with the outside world (USB, PCMCIA slot, memory card ports) are covered with special plugs, and the main focus in communication with the outside world is on wireless communication - for this purpose, a special encryption key is used that cannot be hacked and thanks to which the PDA cannot be detected - however, this entails the main disadvantage of this PDA, which is that unlike the Model 2.0 and Model 3.0 PDAs, the Kulon PDA cannot rely on encryption key sets, thereby it cannot gain direct access to network-connected devices to receive data, but, it can intercept and redirect other special encryption keys, and as a result, gain access to victim GPS.\n \nThis PDA belonged to the stalker Senya Snap.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] extremely low electric power consumption\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] cannot break\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] can be deciphered by technician\n
		</text>
	</string>
</string_table>